ALYSSA CUCUNATO

CONTACT

(856) 287-3779

acucunato18@gmail.com

www.alyssacucunato.com

github.com/acucunato

linkedin.com/in/alyssacucunato

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
- React.js, Material-UI
- JavaScript, jQuery
- JSON, REST, AJAX, APIs
- Express.js
- Node.js
- MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose
- Git, Github, VSCode Editor, application deployment using Heroku
- Exposure to testing using TDD method.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

Philadelphia, PA
Full-Stack Web Development Program
November 2019 – May 2020

PHILADELPHIA UNIVERSITY

Philadelphia, PA B.S. Fashion Merchandising August 2007 – May 2011

Study Abroad, American University of Rome, Fashion Merchandising

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer leveraging a background in retail management to build a more intuitive, polished user experience on the web. Effective at combining creativity and problem-solving skills while concentrating on details no matter the complexity of the project. Equipped in working collaboratively with like-minded team members to ensure optimal results for user and technology-centered designs.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

MAJJ, MERN STACK APPLICATION | majj.app | github.com/jsmithxyz/majj

My Role: Creating & Designing Front-End Experience; Back-End Routing, Group Size: 4

A React-based web application that serves the user fresh content from thousands of providers, presenting the ability to conveniently view and save articles for your reading pleasure all in a single location.

TRIP TIPS WEB APPLICATION | grouptriptips.herokuapp.com | github.com/acucunato/Project-2-Eull-Stack-App My Role: Creating & Designing Front-End Experience; Back-End Routing to Server, Group Size: 4

A full-stack web application that assists the user in creating, viewing, and reviewing user-generated trip itineraries including itineraries for the most visited cities in the US.

 $\textbf{POOCH QUEST WEB APPLICATION} \ | \ accucunato_github_io/pooch-quest/ \ | \ github_com/accucunato/pooch-quest/ \ | \$

My Role: Full-Stack Development, Group Size: 4

An application that assists the user in finding their perfect dog. As soon as the user searches, Pooch Quest gives relevant information about their desired breed along with adoptable dogs in their area.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR STORE OPERATIONS SPECIALIST | Henri Bendel, New York, NY | 2018 - 2019

- Supported smooth store operations by managing all store communications, sending weekly emails, updating the communication portal, maintaining knowledge of products, incentives, and store programs.
- Designed and distributed new management on-boarding training guide that resulted in consistent and seamless onboarding of new management staff, and reduced training time by 50%.
- Established and launched Bendel Experience Program across 28 stores, improving customer in-store experience 35%.

STORE MANAGER | Henri Bendel, Cherry Hill, NJ | Santa Clara, CA | King of Prussia, PA | 2014 - 2018

- Increased store sales in Santa Clara 15% by analyzing key business metrics, identifying opportunities, and implementing impactful solutions, including adjusting store goals and objectives.
- Launched store social media program at King of Prussia store, managing monthly Instagram calendar, partnering with marketing and public relations team to promote in-store events and curate content.
- Trained and on-boarded new store managers company-wide, and acted as area manager, completing weekly store visits to complete visual walk-throughs and provide constructive feedback.

CO-MANAGER | Henri Bendel, Cherry Hill, NJ | 2011 - 2014

- Managed store operations for luxury department store and oversaw sales while providing excellent leadership and guidance to staff members.
- Surpassed sales plan by 10% in first year, and by 15% over prior year in 2013.
- Recruited and trained #1 seller in store, ranked top 20 company wide, who was responsible for 30% of store sales volume.